{
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Which of the following commercial vehicles from Grand Theft Auto IV did NOT reappear in Grand Theft Auto V?",
      "correct_answer": "Steed",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Mule", "Benson", "Pony"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "How many copies of the notorious E.T. game for the Atari 2600 did Atari end up selling?",
      "correct_answer": "1.5 Million",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "1 Million",
        "250 Thousand",
        "Less than 250 Thousand"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Which video game was recalled for containing a hidden, playable South Park episode?",
      "correct_answer": "Tiger Woods 99 PGA Tour",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Tony Hawk&#039;s Pro Skater 3",
        "Sonic Adventure",
        "Madden 99"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "In the Gamecube Version of &quot;Resident Evil&quot; what text document is open on the monitor of the computer in the Visual Data Room?",
      "correct_answer": "A GDC Document",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Text Document on Herbs",
        "Nothing",
        "Document on B.O.Ws"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "In the original &quot;Super Mario Bros.&quot;, what is the acceleration of Mario if he was in free fall?",
      "correct_answer": "91.28 m/s^2",
      "incorrect_answers": ["110  m/s^2", "9.42  m/s^2", "4.4  m/s^2"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "In the Animal Crossing series, which flower is erroneously called the &quot;Jacob&#039;s Ladder&quot;?",
      "correct_answer": "Lily of the Valley",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Hydrangea", "Harebell", "Yarrow"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "When was the first &quot;Half-Life&quot; released?",
      "correct_answer": "1998",
      "incorrect_answers": ["2004", "1999", "1997"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "What is the main theme song of &quot;Sonic Adventure 2&quot;?",
      "correct_answer": "Live and Learn",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Open Your Heart",
        "Can You Feel the Sunshine?",
        "His World"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "What is the fastest speed possible in Trackmania&sup2;: Stadium?",
      "correct_answer": "1000  km/h",
      "incorrect_answers": ["500 km/h", "320 km/h", "100 km/h"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "In World of Warcraft lore, who organized the creation of the Paladins?",
      "correct_answer": "Alonsus Faol",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Uther the Lightbringer",
        "Alexandros Mograine",
        "Sargeras, The Daemon Lord"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "In the game &quot;Overwatch,&quot; which quote does the hero &quot;McCree&quot; NOT say upon using his flashbang ability?",
      "correct_answer": "&quot;You done?&quot;",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "&quot;Whoa there.&quot;",
        "&quot;Hold up now.&quot;",
        "&quot;Don&#039;t move.&quot;"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Which souls game was not directed by Hidetaka Miyazaki?",
      "correct_answer": "Dark Souls 2",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Demon Souls", "Dark Souls", "Dark Souls 3"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "In the National Pokedex what number is Porygon-Z?",
      "correct_answer": "474",
      "incorrect_answers": ["376", "432", "589"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "In Counter Strike: Global Offensive, what is the code implanted onto the C4 as the Terrorists plant the bomb?",
      "correct_answer": "7355608",
      "incorrect_answers": ["7890728", "7256380", "7726354"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "In Xenoblade Chronicles X, which class has a sniper rifle as it&#039;s primary weapon?",
      "correct_answer": "Partisan Eagle",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Blast Fencer", "Winged Viper", "Bastion Warrior"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "In the game Danganronpa: Happy Trigger Havoc, the character Aoi Asahina&#039;s ultimate ability is what?",
      "correct_answer": "Ultimate Swimmer",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Ultimate Detective",
        "Ultimate Gambler",
        "Ultimate Dancer"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Which Kingdom Hearts game featured the cast of &quot;The World Ends With You&quot;?",
      "correct_answer": "Dream Drop Distance",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Birth By Sleep",
        "365/2 Days",
        "Re:Chain of Memories"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "In Animal Crossing: New Leaf, which of these paintings from Redd&#039;s Art Gallery is always genuine?",
      "correct_answer": "Warm Painting",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Jolly Painting",
        "Neutral Painting",
        "Wistful Painting"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "The voice actor for which Portal 2 character was not a TV or film actor prior to the game?",
      "correct_answer": "GLaDOS",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Cave Johnson", "Wheatley", "Atlas / P-Body"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "In the title of the game &quot;Luigi&#039;s Mansion&quot;, what is the only letter to not appear with a pair of eyes in it?",
      "correct_answer": "s",
      "incorrect_answers": ["n", "i", "m"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "How many playable characters are there in Super Smash Bros. for Nintendo 3DS and Wii U?",
      "correct_answer": "58",
      "incorrect_answers": ["48", "51", "55"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "During development of &quot;Super Mario World&quot;, Yoshi&#039;s hard saddle was originally which of these?",
      "correct_answer": "A shell",
      "incorrect_answers": ["A slide of Gelatin", "A poffin", "A spike"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "How many voice channels does the Super Nintendo Entertainment System support?",
      "correct_answer": "8",
      "incorrect_answers": ["6", "10", "12"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "The &#039;D&#039; in the term &quot;D-Mail&quot; from the game &quot;Steins; Gate&quot; is short for what?",
      "correct_answer": "DeLorean",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Deep", "Demo", "Dev"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Which character from the Mega Man series made a small cameo on Volt Catfish&#039;s introduction scene in CD versions of Mega Man X3?",
      "correct_answer": "Auto",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Eddie", "Tango", "Rush"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Which of these games was NOT developed by Markus Persson?",
      "correct_answer": "Dwarf Fortress",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Minecraft", "Wurm Online", "0x10c"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "In &quot;Earthbound&quot;, how does one enter &quot;Master Belch&#039;s&quot; factory?",
      "correct_answer": "Wait 3 Minutes",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Enter the password &quot;Fly Honey&quot;",
        "Enter the password &quot;Master Belch Rules&quot;",
        "Enter the password &quot;Mr Saturn Drools&quot;"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "In the Zombies mode of &quot;Call of Duty: Black Ops&quot;, what is the &quot;Pack-A-Punched&quot; version of the &quot;Galil&quot; called?",
      "correct_answer": "Lamentation",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Galvanized Atomic Lead Insertion Liquidator",
        "Gabig",
        "Predictive Death Wish"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "In &quot;Super Mario Sunshine&quot;, how do you unlock the &quot;Corona Mountain&quot; level?",
      "correct_answer": "By clearing every 7th episode",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "By obtaining 70 Shines",
        "By clearing every episode involving a &quot;Secret&quot;",
        "By unlocking every nozzle F.L.U.D.D can use"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "How many aces can be shot down through the entirety of &quot;Ace Combat Zero: The Belkan War&quot;?",
      "correct_answer": "169",
      "incorrect_answers": ["100", "132", "245"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Which game in the &quot;Monster Hunter&quot; series introduced the &quot;Insect Glaive&quot; weapon?",
      "correct_answer": "Monster Hunter 4",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Monster Hunter Freedom",
        "Monster Hunter Stories",
        "Monster Hunter 2"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "In &quot;Starbound&quot;, what is the max HP of the monster &quot;Punchy&quot;?",
      "correct_answer": "50,000 HP",
      "incorrect_answers": ["9,000,000 HP", "100 HP", "150,000 HP"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Which game in the &quot;Dark Souls&quot; series does the player play as the &quot;Ashen One&quot;?",
      "correct_answer": "Dark Souls III",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Dark Souls I", "Bloodborne", "Demon Souls"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "What was the first &quot;Call Of Duty: Zombies&quot; map to be directed by Jason Blundell?",
      "correct_answer": "Mob Of The Dead",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Buried", "Origins", "Moon"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Which artist composed the original soundtrack for &quot;Watch Dogs 2&quot;?",
      "correct_answer": "Hudson Mohawke",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Rustie", "Machinedrum", "Flying Lotus"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Which of these characters wasn&#039;t a villian in Club Penguin?",
      "correct_answer": "The Director",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Herbert P. Bear",
        "Tusk",
        "Ultimate Proto-Bot 10000"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "In &quot;Team Fortress 2&quot;, what is the fastest taunt kill that can be pulled off?",
      "correct_answer": "Showdown",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Hadouken", "Organ Grinder", "Skewer"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "In &quot;Pok&eacute;mon Sun and Moon&quot;, Team Skull took over which town?",
      "correct_answer": "Po Town",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Heahea City", "Tapu Village", "Iki Town"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "What was the name of Sonic the Hedgehog&#039;s original human girlfriend?",
      "correct_answer": "Madonna",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Celeste", "Sierra", "Nina"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "What Pok&eacute;mon&#039;s Base Stat Total does not change when it evolves?",
      "correct_answer": "Scyther",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Pikachu", "Sneasel", "Larvesta"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "In the &quot;Pikmin&quot; games, which of the following pikmin colors lacks it&#039;s own &quot;Onion&quot; nest?",
      "correct_answer": "Purple",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Winged", "Blue", "Rock"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "In Disney&#039;s &quot;Toontown Online&quot;, which of these species wasn&#039;t available as a Toon?",
      "correct_answer": "Cow",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Monkey", "Bear", "Pig"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "In 2004, which person(s) created &quot;Roblox&quot;?",
      "correct_answer": "David Baszucki and Erik Cassel",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Erik Cassel",
        "Jonas Alto and Sarah Smith",
        "James Kolein"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Which occupation did John Tanner, the main protagonist for Driver and Driver 2, had before turning into an undercover cop?",
      "correct_answer": "Racing Driver",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Taxi Driver", "Delivery Driver", "Getaway Driver"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Which of these characters from Final Fantasy VIII primarily spoke in one word sentences?",
      "correct_answer": "Fujin",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Raijin", "Seifer", "Zell"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "What Touhou Project character&#039;s first ever appearance was as a midboss in the eighth game, Imperishable Night?",
      "correct_answer": "Tewi Inaba",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Mystia Lorelei", "Kaguya Houraisan", "Rumia"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "How many partners can you obtain in Paper Mario: The Thousand-Year Door?",
      "correct_answer": "7",
      "incorrect_answers": ["6", "9", "10"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "In the game Enter the Gungeon, which one of these is not a playable character?",
      "correct_answer": "The Wizard",
      "incorrect_answers": ["The Bullet", "The Robot", "The Cultist"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "In the Nintendo Game Splatoon 2, what is Marina&#039;s screen name?",
      "correct_answer": "DJ_Hyperfresh",
      "incorrect_answers": ["MC.princess", "Kidnotsquid123", "I&lt;30ffTh3H00k"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "In Terraria, which debuff does the ankh charm not provide immunity to?",
      "correct_answer": "Venom",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Cursed", "Bleeding", "Slow"]
    }
  ]
}
